phpfox.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - phpFox Social Network

### 1\. privacy policy

We keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will reflect any updates within this notice.

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. Any such changes will appear here and become effective immediately.

### 2\. our commitment to privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### 3\. The information we collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any of phpFox websites. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are what you provide to us when you complete membership registration and purchase licenses or services on our sites, subscribe to a newsletter.

  The most common types of information we collect include things like: first and last names, email addresses, phones, company number, IP addresses, login history with browser information, payment information with transactional details, and information you provided in support tickets. We also collect web analytics data using [Google Tag Manager](https://www.google.com/analytics/tag-manager/) and [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/).

### 4\. How we use your personal information

phpFox uses the personal data you provide when placing an order or when contacting us only to handle orders, delivers products and services and processes your service requests. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete an order, or under your permission on store app purchasing

.  

STORE APPS PURCHASING

When you purchase an app in the phpFox store (located at [https://store.phpfox.com](https://store.phpfox.com/)), you agree to the the Store terms of usage and according Expert’s terms of usage. When an app purchase is completed, we will send the following information to the Expert’s Web hook Endpoint: Your Name, Your Email, your active URL, and PayPal’s returned transaction detail. This information is necessary for third-party Experts to identify you as a valid purchaser so that they can support you.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### 5\. How You Can Access Your Personal Information

You can access to the personal information that you provide to us in our [Client Area](https://clients.phpfox.com/clientarea.php) >> [Account Detail section](https://clients.phpfox.com/clientarea.php?action=details). You can also see your History email in the [Email History section](https://clients.phpfox.com/clientarea.php?action=emails). You can also access to your orders and invoices in [Billing section](https://clients.phpfox.com/clientarea.php?action=invoices).

  You can also [Contact Us](https://clients.phpfox.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=1) to request for a FULL EXPORT of your data, including your Profile data, Invoices, Product and Services, Email history, Transaction history, and even Activity Logs. We will export and provide you a JSON file comprising all your requested information _within 30 calendar days_.

### 6\. How You Control or Delete Your Information

In case you find that your personal information is incorrect and you want us to update, please contact us by [opening a ticket](https://clients.phpfox.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=1).

  If you are no long want to leave your data at our server, please [submit a ticket](https://clients.phpfox.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=1) to ask for account removal.

### 7\. Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Modifications to Privacy Policy

Amendments to this Privacy Policy may be made by phpFox at any time and you should check back frequently for any changes. We will also provide public notice of changes to this policy on the [Company Blog](https://www.phpfox.com/blog/). Unless otherwise directed by you in writing to us, you agree that phpFox has the right and ability to amend this Privacy Policy at our sole and absolute discretion. This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.
